A Guide to the Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution Agency Head Correspondence and Subject Files, 1980-2012
Library of Virginia
- Agency head correspondence and subject files, 1980-2006.
  - Accession 50472, 1980-2006.
    - DHRM Contract Temp Report Requirement, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - DIT Contract Agreement, 2002-2003. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - DIT TSRs and other DIT info, 2003-2004. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - DIT TSRs and Phone Info, 2001-2002. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - DIT Voice Automation Discussions, 2001. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Division of Hearings creation, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Due Diligence, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Due Diligence Update, 2003. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - EDR Interal Complaints, 2005-2006. (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - EDR Law Student Advocate Project, FY 2005. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - EDR Litigation File, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - EDR Referrals to Internal Auditor, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - EDR Reorganization Info, 2000. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - EDR Restructure, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - EDR Restructure, 2001. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - EDR Salary Study Info, 2000. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - EDR Staff Development, FY 2003. (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - EDR Staff Retreat, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - EDR Strategic Plan, FY 2003. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - EDR Strategic Planning, FY 2004. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - EDR-VITA Email Consolidating Contract, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - EDR Website Info, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Employee Service Awards 2004-2006, 2004-2006. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Energy Report, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Enterprise Business Architecture, 2004-2005. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - EO 52 Analysis Goals and Strategies-Safety, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - EO 52 99 Report-EO 94(05) Report, FY 2006. (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - EO 94(05) Workplace Safety and Employee Health Loss Control Reports, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - E-Procurement Technology Survey, 2000. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - ESP Information, 2004-2005. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - eVA Performance Measure Analysis, FY 2004. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Executive Agreement-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Executive Agreement-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Executive Agreement Results-backup documentation, FY 2004--3rd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Executive Agreement Results-backup documentation, FY 2004--3rd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Executive Agreement-Warner Administration, FY 2002. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Executive Leadership Workshop-Warner Administration, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Executive Order 6 List of Meetings, FY 2004. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Facilitation Services Agreement, 2003. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - General Assembly, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly and DERC Issues, 1994. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - G-Form Info, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Government Business Product Workshop, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Government Performance Project Response-Hiring Processes Data, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Government Performance Project Survey, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Government Performance Project Survey-Grievances, 2003-2004. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Government Performance Project Survey-IT, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Governor's Management Scorecard-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Governor's Management Scorecard-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Governor's Management Scorecard Info, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Management Scorecard Info, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Guidance documents, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Hearing Stats-backup documentation, FY 2004-FY 2006. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hearing Stats-backup documentation, FY 2004-FY 2006. (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Interagency Agreements, 1978-1997. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Internet and Electronic Communications Policy 1.75, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Internet and Electronic Communications Policy Staff Receipt, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Issues Assessment, 1997-1998. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - IT Policy Standards Guidelines, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - JLARC Aging Population Survey, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - JLARC Request on Aging Population, FY 2005. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - JLARC State Report Survey Request, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - JLARC Survey of Information Technology Systems Development, FY 2002. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - JLARC Survey on VITA, FY 2005. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Key Objectives Project-DPB, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Legislation, FY 1999. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Legislation, 2001. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Legislation, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mail Services Survey, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Management Scorecard-backup documentation, FY 2005. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Management Scorecard-backup documentation, FY 2005. (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Mandatory Agency Vehicle Report Data, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Mediation Program History, 1989-2000. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - MOU-EDR and VITA, 2005-2006. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New Grievance Procedure System, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - New IT Projects for FY 2005, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Office Space Questionnaire, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - OSHA's 300 Reporting Requirement, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Past Decision Packages, FY 2003-FY 2005. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Performance Measures-backup documentation, FY 2003-FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Performance Measures-backup documentation, FY 2003-FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Performance Measures-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Performance Measures-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Performance Measures-backup documentation, FY 2006. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Performance Measures-backup documentation, FY 2006. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Performance Measures/Executive Agreement Info-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Performance Measures/Executive Agreement Info-backup documentation, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Permanently Assigned State Vehicle, FY 2003. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Pilot Project, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Plano Meeting Info, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Publications Sent to Library, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Quarterly Results-backup documentation, FY 2005. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Quarterly Results Stats, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Quarterly Results Stats, FY 2004. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Quarterly Stats-backup documentation, FY 2005--2nd quarter. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Report on Urban Economic Growth and Stability, 2000. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Ruling Statistics, FY 2002. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Secretary's Quarterly Report, FY 2005. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Secretary's Quarterly Report, FY 2005. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Seminars and Conferences, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Significant Accomplishments, 1998-2005. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Small Business Survey Response, 2004. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - SOA Info-Legislation Info, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - State Employee Fraud, Waste and Abuse Coordinator, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Strategic Plan and Service Area Plan, FY 2005. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Plan Update, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Plan Update, 2003. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Strategic plans, FY 2002-FY 2003. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Training Session II, FY 2005. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Suggestions for increased efficiencies, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Survey Va. Master Plan, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - SWAM Information, 2002. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - SWAM Plan Info, FY 2003. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - SWAM Plan Info, FY 2004. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - SWAM Plan Info, FY 2005. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - SWAM Plan Info, FY 2006. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Technology Strategic Plan, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Telecommuting Survey, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Training Classes, 2000-2001. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - VDEM State Hazard Mitigation Plan, 2004. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Veteran Status, 2001. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Videoconferencing Use During Management Steps, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Council on Human Rights, 2001. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Meeting Planning-EO 6, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Virginia State Documents, 2002. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Virginia State Documents, 2004. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Virginia State Documents Requirements, 2005. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - VITA CATT Team meeting, 2004. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - VITA Contingency Management Survey, 2001. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - VITA Contingency Management Survey, 2003. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - VITA Customer Satisfaction Survey Meeting, 2004. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - VITA Disaster Recovery Info Provided, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - VITA Info, 2003-2005. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - VITA Mapping to Enterprise Business Model, 2004-2005. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - VITA Meeting-computer issues, 2004. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary of Administration, 2005. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary of Administration-File 1, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary of Administration-File 2, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Worker's Comp Reports, FY 2005. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Accession 51872, 2000-2012.
    - AG monthly reports, 2011. (Box 2)
    - AG monthly reportsd, 2012. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence, 2007. (Box 1)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (received), FY 2008. (Box 1)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (sent), FY 2008. (Box 1)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (received), 2009. (Box 1)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (sent), 2009. (Box 1)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (received), FY 2010. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (sent), FY 2010. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (received), FY 2011. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (sent), FY 2011. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (received), FY 2012. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head chronological correspondence (sent), FY 2012. (Box 2)
    - Agency Head meetings, FY 2008. (Box 1)
    - Agency hiring requests, FY 2008. (Box 1)
    - Agency hiring requests, 2009. (Box 1)
    - Agency hiring requests, FY 2010. (Box 2)
    - Agency hiring requests, FY 2012. (Box 2)
    - Approved reductions, FY 2009. (Box 1)
    - Bane correspondence, FY 2004. (Box 1)
    - Bratschi correspondence, FY 2004. (Box 1)
    - Budget information, 2011. (Box 2)
    - EDR complaints, 2007. (Box 1)
    - EDR monthly reports, 2011. (Box 2)
    - EDR monthly reports, 2012. (Box 2)
    - EO19 Veterans Services Report, FY 2007. (Box 1)
    - General Assembly session, 2007. (Box 1)
    - General Assembly session, LAS, 2009. (Box 1)
    - Governor's Reform Survey Response, FY 2010. (Box 2)
    - Internal monthly reports, 2009. (Box 1)
    - Legislation, 2007. (Box 1)
    - Legislation, 2008. (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2000-2002. (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2007. (Box 1)
    - MOA (EDR and WAH), 2008. (Box 1)
    - Monthly reports, 2008 Jan-Dec. (Box 1)
    - North Highland security audit, FY 2011. (Box 2)
    - Notices received from courts, 2007. (Box 1)
    - Report of Aging Population, 2007. (Box 1)
    - SOA reports, 2007 Jan-May. (Box 1)
    - SOA reports, 2007 June-Dec. (Box 1)
    - SOA reports, 2009. (Box 1)
    - SOA reports, 2010. (Box 2)
    - SOA reports, FY 2011. (Box 2)
    - SOA reports, 2012. (Box 2)
    - Virginia State Library document listing, 2007. (Box 1)
    - VITA information, FY 2010. (Box 2)